approvedfood.co.uk 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Approved Food

## General Privacy Policy

To be viewed along with our standard Terms & Conditions and Cookie Policy

  1. By accessing any part of the Website, you shall be deemed to have accepted this?Privacy Policy in full.?If you do not accept these terms in full, you must leave the Website immediately.

  2. Approved Food may revise this policy at any time by updating this posting. You should check the Website from time to time to review the then current terms, because they are binding on you. Certain provisions of this policy may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages on the Website.

  3. Approved Food Ltd. operates websites with the following domains?approvedfood.co.uk and approvedfood.biz.

**Controllers of Personal Information**

Any personal information provided to or gathered by Approved Food is controlled by Approved Food Ltd., ?(the data controllers) at?Houghton Road,?North Anston Trading Est.,?Sheffield,?S25 4JJ, UK Fast acts as data processor on behalf of the data controllers.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Approved Food Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience at Approved Food. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as bargain alerts, favourites, feedback and recommend products that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our store and platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

Here are the types of information we gather.

  * **Information You Give Us:** we receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way.?You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customising future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

  * **Automatic Information:** we receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our websites.

  * **E-mail Communications:** to help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Approved Food if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Account Details

**What Information Can I Access?**

Approved Food gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Approved Food for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.?This list will change as our website evolves.

## Visitors to our websites

When someone visits Approved Food we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting any of our websites. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

## Credit card details

We **DO NOT STORE** any of your payment / credit card details in our system, all such details are stored with the payment gateway paypal.

## Cookies Policy

Please review our dedicated Cookie Policy page for detailed information including how to Opt Out.

## Access to sales information

We will access the information recorded through your past purchases help us improve our service to you and contact you with special offers that are likely to interest you.

For example, if you buy olive oil from us we might send you an email of when we have a simular product or brand.

## Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United Kingdom. We take reasonable measures to protect your information against unauthorised access or disclosure including physical security, encryption, passwords, etc. However, 3rd parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

## Disclosures of your information

Your information may be passed to and used by all Approved Food Ltd companies. We will never pass your personal data to anyone else, except for any successors in title to our business and suppliers that process data on our behalf. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individual customers are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.

## Sale of Business

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to Approved Food Limited, Approved Food Limited reserves the right to include any or all stored personal information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company. Such an acquisition we will notify all of our business partners.

## Policy Changes

This privacy policy is subject to change without any notice. We may change our policy at any time by posting a new version of it on our website. The effective date of this policy to be applied is 1st July 2009. Any changes to this policy will be posted here.

If you have any questions or concerns relating to this please contact us
